listoviral.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy - Listoviral

Hello! You should know that we collect some information from you when you visit this website. If you choose to become a subscriber to this website, we will collect your email and username. That way we can send you out the posts you want to see. Note that by subscribing to our social media pages is different. We do not own or are responsible for any data that you hand over to social networking sites such as Facebook. You are adhering to their respective terms and conditions.

**Cookie Policy**

The cookie policy on **listoviral.com** is intended to let our readers know about the technology we use called cookies. The policy here is written to help you make the informed decision to suit your needs without doing anything with your data behind your back.

**A detailed explanation about what web cookies are and what they do**

A cookie on the web is a text file that a website’s computer asks your computer to store that file. The text file will then sit on your computer’s hard drive. Information we collect on that data includes statistics such as your time of visit, what you looked at and how long you stayed on a page. Cookies are useful for website owners and advertisers to better understand you. If you are one of the people who complain about not seeing target advertising, you should seriously consider allowing permissions for cookies. It’s the cookie that pings back keywords to ad sources which then try and match those keywords with a subject you are interested in. A person like yourself always has control on allowing or disabling cookies; however, turning the cookies off will result in it being impossible for us and our advertising partners such as Google to know what might interest you. You can read up on more information about cookies here: https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/

**How you can opt out and block the cookies if you feel it’s an invasion of your privacy**

Some people dislike the idea of a machine tracking bits of information about them. The thing is that it’s the only way machines can better target content for you — there is no other way to do it. Most people don’t mind, but if you are one of the people who dislike it, you can block the cookies from your browser Settings. In case you don’t already know, a browser is what you use for browsing the internet. While many think that Internet Explorer is the ‘Internet’, it’s really just one way to browse the Internet. Other browsers apart from Internet Explorer include the new Microsoft Edge browser, Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox and Safari for mobile.

**Google AdSense, the DART cookie and other advertisements.**

Along with our content and advertisements which are our main revenue stream. We run ads from several different advertising networks, the largest of which is Google and their own AdSense advertisements.

Google is a third-party vendor here and they use cookies to help display relevant ads to better suit the readers. Doing so helps the readers so they see ads they might be interested in rather than irrelevant ads that are usually considering more of a nuisance. The cookie Google uses is the Google DART cookie. Visitors to our website can choose to disable that cookie at any time from their own computers browser menu. To find out more about Google ads, please visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy page.

**Third-party links**

Sometimes we give links to content from around the web. These are what are called third-party links. Sometimes those links we give are for navigation to other information only, and other times we might sell those links as ads.

**Third-Party Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:  
_https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp_

**Disclosure**

We do not disclose your information to any other sources outside of this website. We do not sell anyone’s information to third-party sources either.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We comply with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). That means we do not collect any information from children under the age of 13 years. Everything you find on this website from products and services is directed at people who are teenagers or older.

**Opt-out From Push Notifications:**

Simply, you just need to clear your web browser’s caches if you want to opt-out from the push notification services.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to the websites privacy policy we are providing here on the page.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We can change the privacy policy at any time heading into the future.

**Contact Us:**

email: admin@listoviral.com
